[The Old Story of Yu Hong]
[Episode 9]
Does that feel good?
It does.
Feels good? Call me hubby then.
What did you say?
Call me hubby.
Call me hubby!
What the hell are you doing?
Why'd you kick me?
What are you doing?
Are you crazy?
What's wrong? We weren't finished.
W-What are you doing?
What the hell is this?
You can go.
I'm not doing business with you anymore.
No, no, no.
Fine, you don't have to call me hubby.
No need. No need.
Okay, okay. We weren't finished.
I'm still in the mood.
We weren't finished. It's not over yet.
What the hell are you doing?
Oh, my God.
W-What's going on here?
How could you... We weren't finished
and you just kicked me out?
How could you do that?
Don't you have any professional ethics?
Nobody does business like this!
Don't push me too far.
If you piss me off,
I'll burn this whole place down.
That'll teach you to act cocky.
Did you hear me?
What's going on here?
I didn't even say anything.
What's wrong with you?
What's gotten into you?
Why are you crying?
All right, calm down.
Don't cry anymore.
It's nothing. What are you crying for?
Go out the back door.
What's going on here?
You're like an actress.
You can cry on cue, then laugh on cue.
Have you lost your mind or something?
You're just taking me for granted
because I like you so much.
I'm telling you.
You just keep pushing your luck.
What the hell is going on every day?
Every one of you
needs a good beating.
Hello.
Page 3565 for me.
Page it 10 times.
Come to the square and pick me up ASAP.
If you're late, I'll kick your ass.
Right.
Kill bugs, kill ants, kill rats!
Roaches and ants, wipe them all out!
If the rats don't die, I'll die!
A secret formula passed down
for generations.
The rats' worst enemy. Works like a charm!
Fine ingredients, expertly combined!
Colorless, odorless, and eco-friendly.
One bite, and the rat is dead.
Big rats, little rats,
they'll all be gone!
No mess, no fuss.
Clean and easy, no more worries.
Everyone who's tried it swears by it.
The whole neighborhood
gives it two thumbs up!
Kill bugs, kill ants, kill rats!
I'll beat you to a pulp!
Once the contract's done,
take it to the accounting department.
Once you've reviewed it,
just put it on my desk.
You had to call me
about this little thing?
All right.
I'm here, I'm here. Gotta go.
You little punk.
Get in my way again,
and I'll smash you to pieces. Got it?
Got it, got it, Mr. Li.
Every damn day...
Easy, Mr. Li.
You're back.
Have some porridge.
Where are you going?
I'm getting you some side dishes.
Are you avoiding me?
Why would I avoid you?
You're my man.
Then call me hubby.
Call me hubby!
Hubby?
That's more like it.
Call me hubby!
Say it!
Call me hubby! Call me hubby!
Say it! Say it! Say it!
Call me hubby...
Say it!
I-I'm busy here.
How many people do you have there?
Just waiting on me?
Okay, okay, okay.
Coming, coming, coming.
Just wait till I wipe the floor
with you guys.
Just wait!
[Meet at our usual place.]
Tired?
What's wrong?
I don't wanna talk to you.
What's gotten into you?
I know you
hate me.
You'd love nothing more
than to see me dead.
But if I die by your hand,
that's exactly how I'd want to go.
What's
with all the sighing?
I'm happy.
You call that happy?
It's just...
I feel like I won't be happy
for much longer.
What are you talking about?
All right, all right, all right.
Did that asshole hit you again?
Where did he hit you? Let me see.
Let me see.
Go away, go away, go away.
Let me see. What are you...
Now you want to take a look?
I'm no man.
It's not your fault.
What does it have to do with you?
I guess I was just born unlucky.
Trust me.
One day, I'll take you away.
Then no one will ever find us.
I'm not afraid of him.
I'm scared...
Scared of what?
I'm sick.
Oh...
Is it contagious?
No, I mean, is it serious?
Don't worry.
My illness only affects women, not men.
Don't. Don't.
Don't get mad.
Look at you...
What's there to be afraid of
when you're sick?
We'll just get you treated.
So what kind of illness do you have?
I'm talking to you.
It's a woman's problem.
Why are you asking?
You wouldn't understand
even if I told you.
I've seen a doctor.
The doctor said it won't kill me.
But it's not easy to cure.
However...
The doctor did say
there's a folk remedy.
What remedy?
The doctor said
I need to get a snake.
The more venomous, the better.
Fight poison with poison.
You know what I mean?
Wait, isn't this a Cantonese restaurant?
How come you serve
pork stew from Northeast China too?
Don't get me started.
Back in the day,
people just wanted to try something new.
But who eats this stuff these days?
If I hadn't started serving
pork stew from Northeast China,
I'm telling you, this place
would've gone under.
I heard from Fatty Li
that he had snake soup
at a Cantonese restaurant.
He even drank that kind of liquor
mixed with snake venom.
Is anyone still eating snake these days?
[Pay Attention to Hygiene]
Back in the day,
these business owners liked to show off
and would splurge on all-snake banquets.
But look at things now.
People are getting laid off,
businesses are going under.
Who's got money to spend on this stuff?
You know,
I bought a snake last month,
and I still haven't sold it.
If you like it,
I'll sell it to you at a loss.
Come, come, come.
Where is it?
Let me show you. Where is it...
Here.
Is this thing venomous?
Very venomous.